<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Sombra&#39;s Blog</title>
    <link>/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Sombra&#39;s Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>sombra.sh</copyright>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 07:26:27 -0800</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Playing With Fire: Finding Validators</title>
      <link>/posts/playing-with-fire-geth-client/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 02 Feb 2023 07:26:27 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/playing-with-fire-geth-client/</guid>
      <description>Here am I once again.. This time, my night thoughts lead me to a very simple rust program that allow you to find (not 100% precise) ethereum validators. Please keep in mind this is a 30&amp;rsquo; research in the middle of the night. It&amp;rsquo;s just an experience for demonstration and education ONLY.
Cents about decentralization and client diversity Back in the day, BTC guys were almost the same as hackativists. By that I mean, they were truly focused on the mission and the WHY behind the idea of cryptocurrency and electronic cash.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Is your Rust code leaking secret info?</title>
      <link>/posts/rust-leaking-secrets/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 27 Jan 2023 18:26:44 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/rust-leaking-secrets/</guid>
      <description>First things first We close the lide of our noteboo and go out to grab a coffee or a beer. The OS detects and start to suspend the tasks saving it to the RAM or even the Disk/SSD. After couple minutes we get back and start to use our computer like there&amp;rsquo;s no tomorrow. While our fingers type as fast as the matrix allows, a bunch of sensetive operations start to happen (decryption, key generation, etc) and we just keep going, taking for granted what our beloved brothers &amp;ndash; system programmers &amp;ndash; did.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Brain Overflow</title>
      <link>/posts/brain-overflow/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 19 Jan 2023 20:24:05 -0800</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/posts/brain-overflow/</guid>
      <description>Brain (Buffer) Overflow What happens if you try to access some &amp;ldquo;extra&amp;rdquo; part of computer memory? What is memory? What could go wrong if our program doesn&amp;rsquo;t check for boundaries? Well, that&amp;rsquo;s what we&amp;rsquo;ll be seing in this post.
Buffers According with our good old friend Wikipedia, buffers can be described as a region of a memory used to temporarily store data while it is being moved from one place to another.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 28 Dec 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>/about/</guid>
      <description>I’m too nerdy for the rockstart, too rock n’ roll for the nerds. I’m an open minded person who tries to challenge the status quo by questioning the obvious things. The WHY drives my curiosity. In computer science I’ve found my passion and was matter of time until I discovered the underground. I’ve worked as a programmer for Artificial intelligence companies, as a Security analyst for tradi banks and as a Red teammer for a defense contractor.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
